There are things on God's Earth that we can't explain and we can't describe.
The Unnamable is a horror film directed by Jean-Paul Ouellette.
Students from Miskatonic University decide to spend the night in the Winthrop house, a spot widely believed to have been haunted for the
past 300 years, ever since Joshua Winthrop was horribly murdered and mutilated by the hideous creature born of his wife.
Howard Damon, played by Charles Klausmeyer.
Randolph Carter, played by Mark Kinsey Stephenson.
Tanya Heller, played by Alexandra Durrell.
Wendy Barnes, played by Laura Albert.
Bruce Weeks, played by Eben Ham.
John Babcock, played by Blane Wheatley.
The Unnamable is a 1988 American horror film directed,
written, and produced by Jean-Paul Ouellette.
It is based on H.
Lovecraft's short story of the same name.
The film is about a group of university students that made the poor
decision to stay overnight in a 'haunted house'.
Mark Kinsey Stephenson played the lead role, Randolph Carter (a well known H.P.
Lovecraft character), alongside Charles King.
The tone is dark.